rentboard.ca 2018-10-19

# The Rent Board of Canada | Privacy Policy

RentBoard.ca respects the privacy of its users. In this document we explain how we use information you supply us via the RentBoard.ca Web site. This privacy policy may be modified in the future. If it is, a new policy will be posted on this web site. 

This statement is used to identify: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected from you through the web site.
  2. How the information is used.
  3. With whom the information may be shared.
  4. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  5. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under RentBoard.ca's control.
  6. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Whenever you create an on-line listing on our site, we ask that you provide a means (either a telephone number and/or E-mail address) by which you may be contacted. The contact information you supply us is displayed with your listing. All private account information collected is stored by RentBoard.ca and is not sold, distributed or licensed to any third party. Rentboard.ca reserves the right to sell, distribute and license data, information, statistics, and reports that are visible to the public. You have a choice of supplying a telephone number, E-mail address or both when entering contact information. The contact information you supply is used by customers to respond to your listing. Your listings may be sent to other rental-related sites for the purpose of giving your listing greater exposure, however all contact information remains on the RentBoard.ca site. 

You may update any of the information you provide via your account. Your account allows you to maintain the on-line listings you create. You may choose to close your account at any time. 

Our site uses "cookies" to identify your session only. You have the option to accept or reject the cookie, and your choice will affect your ability to access our site. The only difference in our site's features if you reject the cookie will be that you will not be able to access your account. Our site's cookies are not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our database and our Web server operate separately from each other, and each is protected by an electronic and physical firewall keeping users' data secure. 

This site may contain links to other sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are 'clicking' to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us at: [info@rentboard.ca](mailto:info@rentboard.ca)
